# ENG. RASHEED ADNAN AL-WAHBANY

Software Developer

### **PROFILE**

I am a software developer with three years of practical experience in efficiently programming websites and Android applications using modern programming languages such as Java, PHP and Python as well as coding and design languages such as XML, HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Currently, I specialize in website development using Django web framework and ASP.net mvc and have great knowledge of Reactjs and Nextjs. We also worked on customizing a copy of the ODOO system I am committed to proactive feature improvement and bug fixing to ensure we develop modern, easy-to-use websites and applications. I am passionate about software development and am confident that I will be an excellent developer. I have excellent interpersonal skills and I can work effectively as part of a team or individually to achieve project goals because we use github, gitlab with GIT version control.

Date and place of birth in Yemen, Taiz, Sharaab Al-Rawanah at 1996/11/6.

Sanaa, yemen

# **EXPERIENCE**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER YEMENTRACK CORPORATION **Sept 2023 - Now** Front-end and back-end areas using (JAVA, C#, ASP.net MVC, JAVASCRIPT, DJANGO, SQLServer, MYSQL, Postgress and APIs ) SOFTWARE DEVELOPER FREELANCER PROJECTS Fab 2022 - Now Front-end and back-end areas using (JAVA, PHP, JAVASCRIPT, DJANGO and APIs) **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER** YEMENBITS for information technology Fab 2022 - May 2023 Sanaa, yemen Front-end and back-end areas of (POS) system using (Python-Django-PostgresSQL) **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER** Abu Noor Al-Deen for Medical Appliances & Drugs July 2022 - Oct 2023 (AND) Sanaa, Yemen Android developer in both front-end and back-end using (Java-PHP) SOFTWARE DEVELOPER MINSATI for information technology

Front-end and back-end areas of (POS - CRM) systems using

# CONTACTS

- rasheed alwahbany @gmail.comrasheed.alwahbany@outlook.com
- +967 774 258 832
- Yemen, Sana'a, Saref, Community Faculity
- 🚺 github.com/RasheedAlwahbany
  - in https://www.linkedin.com/in/rasheedalwahbai
- 🚹 https://www.facebook.com/rasheedalwahbany

Python

GitLab

**Bootstrap** 

#### SKILLS

**JAVA** 

Git

**DJANGO** PHP NextJS ASP.net **PostgresSQL** ReactJS MySQL **SQL Server** MICROSOFT OFFICE Analyst Team Work Creativity **Flexibility** Responsibility **Android Apps** 

GitHub WEBSITES

# LANGUAGES

Arabic English

# **HOPPIES**

Coding Learning

Listening to the music

# **EDUCATION**

Apr 2022 - Fab 2022

**UNEVERSITY** Sana'a University Bachelor degree in Computer Science (CS) in very good appreciation June 2016 - Sept 2020 HIGH SCHOOL

(Python-Django-PostgresSQL)

2012 - 2015

Taiz Secondary High School

# **PROJECTS**

MOBILE DEVELOPER

Sept 2022 - Mar 2023 HANDYPROANDROID SHOPPING APPLICATION

Android application as freelancer work using (Java-PHP)

June 2022 - Sept 2022 LABORATORIES EQUIPEMENT MENTAINANCE SUPERVISORE

Android application for (AND) Abu Noor Al-Deen for Medical Appliances & Drugs using (Java-PHP)

**BLOOD DONATIONS SUPERVISOR** 

Student graduation project for manage blood donation center needs using (Java-PHP)

IKRAM AL-NAAMA SUPERVISOR FOR YFB Sept 2022 - Mar 2023

(YFB) Yemen Food Bank Ikram Al-Naamah Supervisor and as my team graduation project using (Java-PHP)

WEB DESIGNER

Sept 2022 - Jun 2023

**AGBAR WEBSITE** Apr 2023 - Jun 2023

Freelancer as work projects using (PHP, Bootstrap AND MYSQL)

FARMACY SHOP, JEWELLRY SHOP AND HIREME

Freelancer as work projects using (Python, Django, SQLLite and Postgres)